http://www.ketubahtree.com/terms-conditions

Terms & Conditions
Details on company policy, shipping and returns.
Terms & ConditionsWelcome to the Ketubah Tree Web Site ("Site"). Please review the following basic terms that govern your use of and purchase of products from our Site. Please note that your use of our Site constitutes your agreement to follow and be bound by those terms (the "Agreement").GENERALWe may from time to time change the terms that govern your use of our Site. Your use of our Site following any such change constitutes your agreement to follow and be bound by the terms as changed.We may change, move or delete portions of, or may add to, our Site from time to time.SITE CONTENTSUnless otherwise noted, all materials, including images, designs and written and other materials that appear as part of this Site (collectively, the "Contents") are copyrights, trademarks and/or other intellectual properties owned, controlled or licensed by Shell Artistree LLC ("Shell Art").You may download or copy the Contents and other downloadable materials displayed on the Site for your personal use only. No right, title or interest in any downloaded materials or software is transferred to you as a result of any such downloading or copying. You may not reproduce (except as noted above), publish, transmit, distribute, display, modify, create derivative works from, sell or participate in any sale of, or exploit in any way, in whole or in part, any of the Contents, the Site, or any related software.You agree that Shell Art may use and/or disclose information about your demographics and use of the Site in any manner that does not reveal your identity.SHELL ART'S COMMUNICATIONS TO YOUYou agree that Shell Art may send electronic mail to you for the purpose of advising you of changes or additions to this Site, about any of Shell Art's products or services, or for such other purpose(s) as Shell Art deems appropriate.DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTIES AND LIABILITYYOU AGREE THAT YOUR USE OF THE SITE IS AT YOUR SOLE RISK. BECAUSE OF THE NUMBER OF POSSIBLE SOURCES OF INFORMATION AVAILABLE THROUGH THE SITE, AND THE INHERENT HAZARDS AND UNCERTAINTIES OF ELECTRONIC DISTRIBUTION, THERE MAY BE DELAYS, OMISSIONS, INACCURACIES OR OTHER PROBLEMS WITH SUCH INFORMATION. IF YOU RELY ON THE SITE OR ANY MATERIAL AVAILABLE THROUGH THE SITE, YOU DO SO AT YOUR OWN RISK. YOU UNDERSTAND THAT YOU ARE SOLELY RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY DAMAGE TO YOUR COMPUTER SYSTEM OR LOSS OF DATA THAT RESULTS FROM ANY MATERIAL AND/OR DATA DOWNLOADED FROM OR OTHERWISE PROVIDED THROUGH THE SITE.THE SITE IS PROVIDED TO YOU AS IS, WITH ALL FAULTS, AND AS AVAILABLE. THE SITE, SHELL ART, AND ITS AFFILIATES, AGENTS AND LICENSORS CANNOT AND DO NOT WARRANT THE ACCURACY, COMPLETENESS, CURRENTNESS, NONINFRINGEMENT, MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE OF THE INFORMATION AVAILABLE THROUGH THE SITE, NOR DO THEY GUARANTEE THAT THE SITE WILL BE ERROR-FREE, OR CONTINUOUSLY AVAILABLE, OR THAT THE SITE WILL BE FREE OF VIRUSES OR OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS.UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES SHALL THE SITE, SHELL ART, OR ITS AFFILIATES, AGENTS OR LICENSORS BE LIABLE TO YOU OR ANYONE ELSE FOR ANY DAMAGES ARISING OUT OF USE OF THE SITE, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, LIABILITY FOR CONSEQUENTIAL, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, INDIRECT OR SIMILAR DAMAGES, EVEN IF WE ARE ADVISED BEFOREHAND OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. (BECAUSE SOME STATES DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF CERTAIN CATEGORIES OF DAMAGES, THE ABOVE LIMITATION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. IN SUCH STATES, THE LIABILITY OF THE SITE, SHELL ART, AND ITS AFFILIATES, AGENTS AND LICENSORS IS LIMITED TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY SUCH STATE LAW.) YOU AGREE THAT THE LIABILITY OF THE SITE, SHELL ART, AND ITS AFFILIATES, AGENTS AND LICENSORS, IF ANY, ARISING OUT OF ANY KIND OF LEGAL CLAIM IN ANY WAY CONNECTED TO THE SITE SHALL NOT EXCEED THE AMOUNT YOU PAID TO SHELL ART FOR THE USE OF THE SITE.INACCURACY DISCLAIMERFrom time to time there may be information on ketubahtree.com that contains typographical errors, inaccuracies, or omissions that may relate to product descriptions, pricing, and availability. We reserve the right to correct any errors, inaccuracies or omissions and to change or update information at any time without prior notice (including after you have submitted your order). We apologize for any inconvenience this may cause you.Before you act on information you've found on the Site, you should confirm any facts that are important to your decision. Shell Art makes no warranty as to the reliability, accuracy, timeliness, usefulness or completeness of the information on the Site.INDEMNIFICATIONYou agree to indemnify, defend and hold harmless Shell Art, its affiliates, and its officers, directors, employees, agents, licensors and suppliers, from and against any and all losses, expenses, damages and costs (including reasonable attorneys' fees) resulting from any violation of this Agreement or any activity related to your account (including negligent or wrongful conduct) by you or any other person accessing the Site using your account.MISCELLANEOUSShell Art is not responsible for, and cannot guarantee, the timely performance of shipping vendors once your order is shipped from it's office/location or it's licensee's location.Shell Art is not responsible for any damage caused to your order by you or any other third party, including calligraphers, once your order is shipped from our offices or from our licensee's office/location.Shell Art reserves the right to use, reproduce, market, and sell any art work that is created by us including but not limited to any custom or commisioned designs.This Agreement shall be construed in accordance with the laws of the Commonwealth of Virginia, without regard to any conflict of law provisions. By using this Site, you consent to the exclusive jurisdiction of the state and federal courts located in Virginia, in all disputes arising out of or relating to this Agreement or use of this Site.In the event that any portion of this Agreement is found to be invalid or unenforceable for any reason, such invalidity or unenforceability shall not affect the enforceability or validity of any other portion of this Agreement, which shall remain in full force and effect and be construed as if the invalid or unenforceable portion were not part of the Agreement.TERMINATIONThis Agreement is effective unless and until terminated by either you or Shell Art. You may terminate this Agreement at any time. Shell Art also may terminate this Agreement at any time and may do so immediately without notice, and accordingly deny you access to the Site, if in Shell Art's sole discretion you fail to comply with any term or provision of this Agreement. Upon any termination of this Agreement by either you or Shell Art, you must promptly destroy all materials downloaded or otherwise obtained from this Site, as well as all copies of such materials, whether made under the terms of this Agreement or otherwise.Privacy PolicyWe respect your privacy. We do not sell, trade or share our customers' personal information (such as name, address, telephone number or credit card number) with any third parties, except where necessary to complete your order or to ship your order and in those cases the only information provided is the information necessary for that specific task. We do not authorize any of these third parties to use your information for any purpose other than for its intended purpose.When you provide us with personal information, through, for example, the registration and ordering process, we collect and use that information in an effort to identify your product preferences, improve your shopping experience and to communicate with you about our products, services, and promotions. If you do not wish for us to use this information for these purposes, please let us know by contacting us.When you visit our site but do not register or place an order, we will not receive any personal information from you. However, we do track the Internet address of the domains from which people visit us and analyze this data for trends and statistics, but the individual user remains anonymous. Some of our Web pages utilize "cookies" so that we can better serve you with more tailored information when you return to our site. Cookies are identifiers which a Web site can send to your browser to keep on your computer to facilitate your next visit to our site. You can set your browser to notify you when you are sent a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. The information we collect and analyze is used to improve our service to you.This site may contain links to other sites that are not under our control. Such sites have their own policies regarding privacy, which you should review before visiting them. We have no responsibility for linked sites and provide these links solely for the convenience and information of our visitors.If our information practices change in the future, we will let you know by posting the policy changes on our site before we use your information in a manner not previously disclosed in this privacy policy. You will, of course, have the opportunity at that time to opt out of any new use of your information. If you have any comments or questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us.
Ketubah Tree
Modern Fine Art Ketubah designs by designer and artist Michelle Shell Rummel Featuring unique and beautiful contemporary Ketubah prints and delicate papercut ketubot
, USA
instagram twitter facebook
